inter.it 2018-03-25

# F.C. Internazionale Milano - Official Website | EN PRIVACY

Open Menu Close Menu Close Menu

  *   * 

Login

To buy   
you must be registered on inter.it 

Already registered?   
Login

Not registered yet?    
Create a profile now.

IT'S EASY, FREE AND THERE ARE EXCLUSIVE BENEFITS

 SIGN UP 

Forgot your password?

Please enter your email address to receive the instructions to create a new password 

  *  Home 
  *  News 
  *  Team 
  *  Season 
  *  Club 
  *  Interisti 

Open User Access

## This website, inter.it (the "Site"), and all personal information collected from users of this Site are owned solely by F. C. Internazionale Milano S.p.A. In this Privacy Policy references to "we", "us" and "our" are references to F. C. Internazionale Milano S.p.A. .

## We take the privacy of our users seriously

This Privacy Policy (the “Policy”) outlines how we treat your personal information and forms part of the “Terms and Conditions” of this Site. This Policy applies only to this Site, and not to the collection and use of personal information by any third party via any website to which there are links on this Site. We are not responsible for the privacy policies of other websites, and encourage you to be aware when you leave our Site.

## Consent

Your use of this Site signifies your consent to our collecting and using information (sometimes personal information) about you in accordance with this Policy. 

## What information do we collect?

You may access this Site's home page and browse the Site without disclosing any personal data. In order to provide you with a range of services, however, we may collect personal information from this Site, which we will ask you for when and if needed. In such cases we will explicitly ask for your permission to process the collected data (for example on the registration page). 

## How do we use your information?

Any personal data relating to you will be used and recorded by us in accordance with current data protection legislation and this Privacy Policy. 

We may use your personal information to communicate with you, such as to let you know about new features or offers on inter.it, for record-keeping purposes, and in aggregate form (and therefore anonymously) for market-research purposes, to track activity on our Site, to publish trends and/or to improve usefulness and content and for any other purpose that we may notify you and the relevant data protection authority about.  
We may operate one or more mailing lists to send you INTER-related news. These mailing lists currently operate as 'opt-in' mailing lists whereby subscribers add themselves to the list. 

We only send emails to addresses which have been subscribed to each list. We do not 'spam'.  
If you wish to unsubscribe from a list (see Unsubscribe below), you can do it from your profile page (as a registered user) or by emailing us at registrazione_sito@inter.it. We currently do not share, license or sell these email addresses.  
We reserve the right to disclose your personal information to anyone who may take over the running of the Site or who may purchase any or all of our assets including your personal information. We reserve the right to disclose your personal information to any law enforcement agency requesting it in connection with the commission of any offence, once we are reasonably satisfied as to the circumstances surrounding the request.  
We also reserve the right to access and disclose your personal information in order to comply with applicable laws and lawful government requests, to operate our systems properly or to protect our users and ourselves. Except as expressly stated in this Policy, we will not sell, share, trade or license your personal information to others without your express consent.

## Security

We take every precaution to protect your personal information. In addition, we have strict security protocols in place to protect our customer database from unauthorised access, improper use or disclosure, unauthorised modification, and unlawful destruction or accidental loss. We only allow access to the customer database when absolutely necessary, and then under strict guidelines as to how such details may be used. We may ask you for proof of identity before disclosing any personal information to you. 

## Surveys

We always aim to improve the services we offer. As a result, we may occasionally canvass our customers using surveys. Participation in surveys is voluntary, and you are under no obligation to reply to any survey you might receive from us. Should you choose to do so, we will treat the information you provide with the same high standard of care as all other customer information. 

## Activities

Your participation on our Site may mean that we occasionally contact you with the opportunity to join activities (such as play online games or enter competitions). Participation in any of these activities is voluntary, and you are under no obligation to take up an invitation from us to participate. Should you choose to join an activity, we will treat the information you provide with the same high standard of care as all other customer information. 

## Cookies

When you visit one of our Sites we may send you a cookie. Usage of cookies is in no way linked to any personally identifiable information while on our Site. A cookie is a small file that can be placed on your computer's hard drive for record-keeping purposes, and we may use them to do a number of things. For example, cookies may be used to compile anonymous statistics related to the take-up or use of services, or browsing patterns. When used in this manner, you are not individually identified, and information collected in this manner is only used in aggregate form. Some of our business partners (such as advertisers) may use cookies on our Site or their own sites. We have no access to, or control over, these cookies. You are not required to accept a cookie from us, or any other website, and you may set your browser so that it will not accept cookies, although some features on the Site may not function if you do. 

## Correcting and updating personal information

If your personal information changes, or if you believe that the personal data we hold about you is incorrect, you may correct it in your profile page or by sending an email to registrazione_sito@inter.it. 

## Unsubscribe

We hope that you will enjoy using this Site and the services we offer. However, you may request that your personal information is not used in the ways outlined above. This is called “Unsubscribing” and may be achieved by any of the following methods: - sign in and visit the profile page, untick the relevant check box(es) and save your details. \- email us at registrazione_sito@inter.it, specifying which services you don’t require anymore. 

## Deletion

At any time you can ask for your personal information to be erased from our databases. This is called “Deletion” and may be achieved by any of the following methods:  
\- sign in and visit the profile page, select the “Cancel my registration” option and follow the instructions given;  
\- email us at registrazione_sito@inter.it and follow the instructions we will email you. 

## Site and service updates

If you are a registered user of the Site, we may send you Site and service announcements or updates. You cannot unsubscribe from service announcements unless you perform a “Deletion”. 

## Notification of changes

We may occasionally modify our Privacy Policy. When this happens, we will notify you via our homepage. 

## Privacy Support

If you have any queries about our Privacy Policy, please email us at privacy@inter.it. 

Inter.it uses cookies of its own and of third parties to collect to simplify and improve browsing. If a browser has blocked the use of cookies, some of the services and functionalities of the website will not be available. 

## What is a cookie?

A cookie is a small fragment of text that websites send to the browser and that are stored in the user's device, such as their personal computer, mobile telephone, tablet, etc. These files are used by the website to remember information about the visit, such as language preferences and other options, while helps to set things up for their next visit and make the website more useful by personalising its content. Cookies play a very important role improving the experience of using the website.[Read more](http://www.garanteprivacy.it/cookie)

## How are cookies used?

By browsing this website, the user is allowing cookies to be installed in their device to tell us the following information: 

  * Statistical information about use of the website. 
  * The user's login, to keep the user logged into the website. 
  * The preferred web format for access from mobile devices. 
  * The most recent searches made of the web's services, and the personalised details of these services. 
  * Information about advertisements that are shown to the user. 
  * Details for connecting to social networks for users that access the site via their Facebook or Twitter accounts. 

## Types of cookie used

**Functional cookies**  
These cookies are mandatory to play highlights, buy tickets or season-rickets; each time you return to inter.it you will not have to type login and password again. 

**Performance and stats cookies**  
QPiwik, Google Analytics e Google Tag Manager

**Social Cookies**  
To share an inter.it page on your facebook profile or twitter timeline.

In depth 

Company | Website | Cookie | Type | Usage  
---|---|---|---|---  
F.C. Internazionale | www.inter.it | Inter | Technical/functional | Your profile  
F.C. Internazionale | interchannel.inter.it | Inter-Piwik | Stats | Analytics  
F.C. Internazionale | giovanili.inter.it | Doubleclick | 3rd parties | Analytics  
F.C. Internazionale | interclub.inter.it | [Google Tag Manager](https://www.google.it/tagmanager/use-policy.html) | 3rd parties | Analytics  
F.C. Internazionale | ccic.inter.it | [Media Math](https://www.mediamath.com/privacy-policy/) | 3rd parties | Analytics  
F.C. Internazionale | intercampus.inter.it | [Google Analytics](https://www.google.it/intl/it_it/policies/technologies/cookies/) | 3rd parties | Analytics  
F.C. Internazionale |  | Instagram | 3rd parties | Analytics  
F.C. Internazionale |  | YouTube | 3rd parties | Analytics  
F.C. Internazionale |  | [Facebook](https://www.facebook.com/help/cookies/) | 3rd parties | Analytics  
F.C. Internazionale |  | [Twitter](https://support.twitter.com/articles/20170519) | 3rd parties | Analytics  
|  Company  
F.C. Internazionale  |  Website  
www.inter.it   
---|---  
Cookie  
Inter  |  Type  
Technical/functional  |  Usage  
Your profile   
---|---|---  
|  Company  
F.C. Internazionale  |  Website  
interchannel.inter.it   
---|---  
Cookie  
Inter-Piwik  |  Type  
Stats  |  Usage  
Il tuo profilo   
---|---|---  
|  Company  
F.C. Internazionale  |  Website  
giovanili.inter.it   
---|---  
Cookie  
Doubleclick  |  Type  
3rd parties  |  Usage  
Your profile   
---|---|---  
|  Company  
F.C. Internazionale  |  Website  
interclub.inter.it   
---|---  
|  Company  
F.C. Internazionale  |  Website  
ccic.inter.it   
---|---  
|  Company  
F.C. Internazionale  |  Website  
intercampus.inter.it   
---|---  
  
Company  
F.C. Internazionale 

|  Cookie  
Instagram  |  Type  
3rd parties  |  Usage  
Analytics   
---|---|---  
  
Company  
F.C. Internazionale 

|  Cookie  
Youtube  |  Type  
3rd parties  |  Usage  
Analytics   
---|---|---  
  
Company  
F.C. Internazionale 

|  Cookie  
[Facebook](https://www.facebook.com/help/cookies/) |  Type  
3rd parties  |  Usage  
Analytics   
---|---|---  
  
Company  
F.C. Internazionale 

|  Cookie  
[Twitter](https://support.twitter.com/articles/20170519) |  Type  
3rd parties  |  Usage  
Analytics   
---|---|---  
  
## How to change your cookie settings? How to block or allow a type of cookie?

  * Internet Explorer: <https://support.microsoft.com/kb/278835>
  * Internet Explorer [windows mobile]: <https://www.windowsphone.com/en-us/how-to/wp7/web/changing-privacy-and-other-browser-settings>
  * Chrome: [https://support.google.com/chrome/bin/answer.py?hl=en-GB&answer=95647](https://support.google.com/chrome/bin/answer.py?hl=en-GB&answer=95647)
  * Safari: <https://docs.info.apple.com/article.html?path=Safari/5.0/en/9277.html>
  * Safari [versione mobile]: <https://support.apple.com/kb/HT1677>
  * Firefox: <https://support.mozilla.org/en-US/kb/Enabling%20and%20disabling%20cookies>
  * Blackberries: <https://docs.blackberry.com/en/smartphone_users/deliverables/32004/Turn_off_cookies_in_the_browser_60_1072866_11.jsp>
  * Android: [https://support.google.com/mobile/bin/answer.py?hl=en&answer=169022](https://support.google.com/mobile/bin/answer.py?hl=en&answer=169022)
  * Opera: <https://www.opera.com/browser/tutorials/security/privacy/>
